verified-p2p-links.com 2011-11-13

# Privacy Policy › isoHunt › P2P and BitTorrent link releases

| 

  * You can use boolean operators ( **-** , **|** , **OR** ), wildcards ( ***** , **?** ), and phrase search ( **"** ) in your query
  * For BitTorrent: Paste in a 40 characters info_hash, to search for that particular torrent and get all trackers for it

| |   
---  

Active torrents indexed from websites and trackers across the internet, unique by info_hash

  Sites: 544  •  Trackers: 181,637  •  **Active Torrents: 8,046,753**  •  Files: 191.53M  •  Size: 13,453.85 TB  •  Peers: 29.08M  

Privacy Policy

isoHunt.com values your privacy. Without writing full blown legalese, in essence, we will never disclose your personal information (email address, IP addresses, etc.) and associated activity on this Web site to any third party, without your permission. We also will not retain your personal information for any longer than necessary for administrative purposes.

### Third Party Advertising

We use various third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that maybe of interest to you.

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. This in itself will not divulge your personal information.

|   

| Stats  
---  
isoHunt has **20187** users online, 1721395 members registered. Sign up now to comment!  
Welcome to our newest member: **_thenobbies_**  
  
Shout Box  
---  
  
You have to login to post. Use your common sense.  
For debates, go to the forum.  
**Post or ask for site invites and you get banned.**  
For real-time chat, come to irc.isohunt.com, #isoHunt

READ! | Smileys
